

www.mywebsite@loiwai.com

www.linkinedin.com/in/loiwai/

Loi Wai

Mathematics & Computer Science Student
University of Papua New Guinea

Mathematics and Computer Science student at University of Papua New Guinea with work experience in the field of IT, good communication skills, and reliable leadership skills. Very Passionate about drive and energy that exist in the technology driven world and the advancement of IT

Personal Details

Given Name: Loi Surname: Wai

Place of origin: Tifalmin, Telefomin District, Sandaun Province, PNG

Nationality: Papua New Guinea

Current Residence: UPNG Waigani campus, Port Moresby, PNG

DOB: 07-02-1998 Gender: Male Marital Status: Single

Education

MajorInstitutionTime of EventPrimary EducationWangbin Primary School2008 - 2013Secondary EducationTabubil Secondary School2014 - 2017

Mathematics Computer Science University of Papua New Guinea 2018 - Current [Final year]

Work Experience

CompanyPositionTime of EventPrivate CarpentryCarpenter2008 - 2017[With Mr. Wai]

Paradise Foods Limited IT & Finance Intern 2019 - 2021 [While at UPNG]

Other Skills

Responsive Web Design | IT Help Desk | Networking

Video shooting & editing Graphic Design Bank Reconciliation & Basic Financing

Referees

Clancy Kees John Baulo Benaiya Nari Wai Lodi

Senior Advisor Career Trackers Indigenous Internship Program

Ph: 1097203702 Mail: jbaulo@pfl.com Network Engineer Paradise Foods Limited Ph: 1097203702

Mail: jbaulo@pfl.com Ph: 109720370:

Mail: jbaulo@pfl.com Mail: jbaulo@pfl.com

Coordinator & Facilitator Senior Carpenter

UPNG Peer Mentorship
Program
Ph: 1097203702
Ph: 1097203702
Mail: jbaulo@pfl.com
jbaulo@pfl.com